TOPIC
    about_containerstoolkit

    Containers-Toolkit contains PowerShell functions that allow you to download,
    install, and configure Containerd, BuildKit, nerdctl, and Windows CNI for
    container networks.

SHORT DESCRIPTION
    Containers-Toolkit contains PowerShell functions that allow you to download,
    install, and configure Containerd, BuildKit, nerdctl, and Windows CNI for
    container networks.

LONG DESCRIPTION
    This is a rudimentary module that allows to download, install, and configure
    Containerd, BuildKit, nerdctl, and Windows CNI for container networks. It
    also allows you to get the list of the container tools and their
    installation statuses.
    Configurations done with these functions are the default configurations that
    allow you to get started with interacting with the tools. Further
    configurations may be necessary.
    You can find documentation for these functions here:    
        https://github.com/microsoft/containers-toolkit/tree/main/docs/command-reference.md

KEYWORDS
    - Containerd
    - BuildKit
    - nerdctl
    - Windows CNI
    - Windows Containers
    - Microsoft Windows

